<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Matrix Code of Conduct</title><link>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/</link><description>Recent content on Matrix Code of Conduct</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Michael Sasser</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Attribution &amp; Acknowledgements</title><link>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/attribution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/attribution/</guid><description>This Code of Conduct is based on the Matrix.org&amp;rsquo;s Code of Conduct, but with some modifications, which is based on the TODO Group&amp;rsquo;s Open Code of Conduct template, but with some modifications.</description></item><item><title>Definitions</title><link>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/definitions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/definitions/</guid><description>Harassment includes, but is not limited to:
Offensive comments related to gender, gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disability, mental illness, neuro(a)typicality, physical appearance, body size, race, age, regional discrimination, political or religious affiliation Unwelcome comments regarding a person’s lifestyle choices and practices, including those related to food, health, parenting, drugs, and employment Deliberate misgendering. This includes deadnaming or persistently using a pronoun that does not correctly reflect a person&amp;rsquo;s gender identity.</description></item><item><title>Diversity Statement</title><link>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/diversity_statement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/diversity_statement/</guid><description>We encourage everyone to participate and are committed to building a community for all. Although we will fail at times, we seek to treat everyone both as fairly and equally as possible. Whenever a participant has made a mistake, we expect them to take responsibility for it. If someone has been harmed or offended, it is our responsibility to listen carefully and respectfully, and do our best to right the wrong.</description></item><item><title>General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)</title><link>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/imprint-gdpr/gdpr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/imprint-gdpr/gdpr/</guid><description>Effective date: January 4, 2021
Accountable person Michael Sasser Benzinoring 56 67657 Kaiserslautern Germany Email address: Michael@MichaelSasser.org Imprint: https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/imprint-gdpr/imprint/
Overview of data processing The following overview summarizes the types of data processed and the purposes of their processing and refers to the data subjects.
Types of data processed Inventory data (e.g. names, nicknames). Content data (e.g. entries in online forms). Contact details (e.g. email, phone numbers). Meta / communication data (e.</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/imprint-gdpr/imprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/imprint-gdpr/imprint/</guid><description>Information according to § 5 TMG
Michael Sasser Benzinoring 56 67657 Kaiserslautern Germany E-Mail: Michael@MichaelSasser.org Responsible for content according to § 55 Abs. 2 RStV: Michael Sasser Benzinoring 56 67657 Kaiserslautern Germany E-Mail: Michael@MichaelSasser.org Disclaimer: Content Liability The contents of our pages were created with great care. However, we can not assume any liability for the accuracy, completeness and timeliness of the content. As a service provider we are responsible according to § 7 Abs.</description></item><item><title>Matrix Code of Conduct</title><link>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/coc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/coc/</guid><description>This code of conduct outlines our expectations for participants within the Matrix community, as well as steps for reporting unacceptable behaviour. We are committed to providing a welcoming and inspiring community for all, and expect our code of conduct to be honoured. Anyone who violates this code of conduct may be banned from the community.
This applies to conversation in the Python room (@Python3:matrix.org).
Our open source community strives to:</description></item><item><title>Reporting Issues</title><link>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/reporting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaelsasser.github.io/matrix-room-python/post/reporting/</guid><description>If you experience or witness unacceptable behaviour — or have any other concerns — please report it by contacting us via abuse@michaelsasser.org. All reports will be handled with discretion. In your report please include:
Your contact information. Names (usernames and nicks, real names, and/or pseudonyms) of any individuals involved. If there are additional witnesses, please include them as well. Your account of what occurred, and if you believe the incident is ongoing.</description></item></channel></rss>